himalayahealthcare.com 2009-01-30

# Liv.52,Pure herbs,Ayurvedic products India,Herbal health care,Herbal care India,Himalaya herbal healthcare,Herbal medicines India,Ayurvedic herbs India,Alternative medicines India,Herbal products India,Natural herbal remedies India

At The Himalaya Drug Company, we respect every individual's right to privacy. Our relationship with you is our most valuable asset and is the very basis of our name and reputation.

We understand the importance you place on the privacy and security of information that personally identifies you or your account information. We refer to and treat this information as "personal information". 

We do reserve the right to disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under law, to co-operate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, or to protect our rights or property.

We use personal information in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which we originally requested it. For example, we will use the information you give us to process your requests and transactions, to provide you with additional information about products and services, or to evaluate your financial needs. To do so, we may share personal information with an agent or affiliate. 

We limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business and to deliver superior service to you. This may include advising you about our products or services, those of our affiliates, and other opportunities that we believe may interest you. To serve you better, we may combine information you give us on the Web or through other channels.

When we share personal information with an agent or affiliate, we protect that personal information with a strict confidentiality agreement. Companies that we hire to provide support services or act as our agent must conform to our privacy standards. 

Himalaya corporate policies require that employees with access to confidential customer information may not use or disclose the information except for business use. All employees are required to safeguard such information, as specified in their confidentiality agreements with Himalaya. 

On occasions, we may assist a company that is not affiliated with Himalaya in providing or offering a product or service to you. In such circumstances, marketing materials will include instructions on how you can request not to receive those communications in the future. In all cases, your personal information is protected by a strict confidentiality agreement. We do not allow any nonaffiliated company to retain your personal information longer than necessary to provide the product, service, or information, unless you affirmatively grant us permission to do so.

We continue to evaluate our efforts to protect personal information and make every effort to keep your personal information accurate and up to date. 

If you identify any error in your personal information or need to make a change to that information, please contact us and we will promptly update our records. 

If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us by e-mail at [write.to.us@himalayahealthcare.com](mailto:write.to.us@himalayahealthcare.com) or call us at + 91 80 23714444 

Cookies

To personalize your experience on our website or with one of our promotions, we may assign your computer browser a unique random number, called a "cookie." Cookies enhance the Himalaya web site performance in several important ways: they personalize your experience on our site, and they make your visit to our site more convenient for you. 

Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from our website. We do not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies can't read data from your computer's hard disk or read cookie files from other Web sites. In addition, companies we may hire to evaluate our Web promotions may set cookies to assist with such an evaluation. Again, neither Himalaya nor companies acting on our behalf use cookies to collect personal information.

|   |
